https://www.ggcomm.com/privacy-policy/

Goldstein Group CommunicationsPrivacy Policy of Goldstein Group Communications, Inc.Goldstein Group Communications, Inc. (GGC) operates the www.ggcomm.com website, which provides marketing and branding sites.This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decides to use the Goldstein Group Communications website.If you choose to visit the GGC site, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for keeping in touch with those who visit us. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at www.ggcomm.com, unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.Information Collection and UseFor a better experience while using our Site, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, phone number, and postal address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.Log DataWe want to inform you that whenever you visit our site, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.CookiesCookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.Our website uses these “cookies” to collection information and to improve our agency sites. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our site.Site ProvidersWe may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:To facilitate our Site;To provide the Site on our behalf;To perform Site-related sites; orTo assist us in analyzing how our Site is used.We want to inform our Site users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.SecurityWe value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links to Other SitesOur Site may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites.Children’s PrivacyOur Sites do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.Contact UsPRIVACY & DATA PROTECTION POLICY (ADDENDUM)Goldstein Group Communications, Inc. has made a commitment to comply with all privacy and data protection requirements imposed by both the US Department of Commerce and the European Union (“EU”). This includes the recent General Data Protection Regulation. To that end, recipients of our electronic communications who have not affirmatively opted in to receive communications will be given an opportunity to do so. Opt-out links will also be provided in all of our electronic communications and on our site to unsubscribe from future communications.In order to service our customers and facilitate future communications and interaction with customers and prospects, we collect and store information on our site through the use of “cookies.” We collect and store only the information required for these purposes. For contacts located in the EU, you will be provided an opportunity to opt into our system by accepting the terms and conditions of both our electronic communications process and website use before we use a “cookie” to collect and store information.We promise to protect all information collected and stored, and upon request we will provide a complete copy of all information stored for the customer or prospective customer. We will also delete all information stored for marketing purposes, including your IP address, upon receipt of any request to delete the information by clicking this link. Goldstein Group Communications reserves the right to continue using the deleted stored information for any “lawful basis,” which includes customer collection purposes.All questions regarding our policy should be directed to webmaster@ggcomm.com.If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
